

# **Nazrul Islam**

Website Developer

### **About Me**

I was born and raised in Dhaka-Bangladesh, and now I'm proud to be raising my young family here. That's why I love helping people find their Dhaka dream home. Having lived and worked here nearly my entire life, my local market knowledge is unparalleled.

## **Expertise Skill**

- Website developer
- CMS expert
- Digital Marketing
- E-commerce expert

#### **Contact Me**

- +880 13039-87527
- info@nazrulshopify.com
- www.nazrulshopify.com
- 1Tejgaon., Dhaka-1208, Bangladesh

### **Education**

- 2014-2017
   Asian University of Bangladesh
   Bachelor of Engineering (BEng),
   Computer engineering
- 2017-2019
   ENGINEERING DEGREE ULAB
   Java: Object-oriented
   programming language known
   for its portability and versatility.

## **Work Experience**

Web Developer Expert

Fiverr | 2019-2023

- Build 300+ website for large company
- complete a lot of complicated work
- Senior Graphic Designer

lliceria & co. | 2020-present

- create more than 100 graphic designs for big companies
- complete a lot of complicated work
- Ensured customer satisfaction by handling dayto-day affairs
- Managing oversees Company digital marketing strategies to reach more client in website and social media.